Guide to the Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection MSS.158
Fales Library and Special Collections
Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection
circa 1958-1998
Fales Library and Special Collections
Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002
MSS.158
103 Linear Feet (94 boxes)
The Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection chronicles the career of Norman "Buddy" Baker in his roles as composer, orchestrator, conductor, and musical director with Walt Disney Studios from the mid 1950s to the 1980s. The bulk of the collection consists of autograph, typed, and photocopied music scores, sketches, lead sheets, musical breakdowns and parts from music composed for Walt Disney theatrical, television, and theme park productions.
Provenance
The Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection was donated to the Fales Library in 2004 by Buddy Baker's wife, Charlotte Baker.
Access Restrictions
Materials are open without restrictions. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Biographical Note
The Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection, consisting of nearly 12,000 pages, chronicles the celebrated career of Norman "Buddy" Baker in his roles as composer, orchestrator, conductor, and musical director with Walt Disney Studios - much of it spent in daily collaboration with Walt Disney. Initially hired as an orchestrator for the 1954 television series Davy Crockett, and appointed as the musical director of the original Mickey Mouse Club in 1955, his twenty-eight years with Disney Studios featured 40 films, 125 television shows, and music for the Disney theme park attractions worldwide, including The Haunted Mansion, Pirates of The Caribbean, and It's A Small World at Disneyland. Among his scores for live-action and animated theatrical features were The Monkey's Uncle (1965), the Cannes award-winning featurette Donald In Mathmagicland, the Oscar-nominated Napoleon and Samantha (1971), and The Fox and The Hound (1981).
He was awarded the accolade Disney Legend in 1998, the Walt Disney Corporation's most prestigious creative award. Honoring his multifaceted career as composer and pedagogue, Buddy was the recipient of the ASCAP Foundation's Lifetime Achievement Award in 1999. Buddy Baker's pre-Disney years, as jazz trumpeter and composer/arranger in the big-band era, featured collaborations with jazz legends Harry James and Stan Kenton. His 1944 arrangement of Stan Kenton's And Her Tears Flowed Like Wine became a Top 10 hit. Buddy also served as music director for the live radio shows of Bob Hope and Jack Benny.
Buddy's music is embedded in American culture through television in The Wonderful World of Color, The Mousketeer Club, and The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh. In the years following Disney's death in 1966, Buddy Baker continued to compose music for many of the attractions and rides throughout the Disney theme parks, including The Haunted Mansion and Pirates of The Caribbean. At one point, Buddy had composed the lion's share of all music heard in the Disney parks worldwide.
Buddy Baker was a pioneer and great proponent of the study of film scoring in higher education. His teaching career began in the 1940's at Los Angeles' City College, where one of his students was Jerry Goldsmith. From 1987 until his death on July 26, 2002 at the age of 84, he was the driving force and Chair of the USC Program in Scoring for Motion Pictures and Television.
Scope and Content Note
The Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection, consisting of nearly 12,000 pages, chronicles the celebrated career of Norman "Buddy" Baker in his roles as composer, orchestrator, conductor, and musical director with Walt Disney Studios - much of it spent in daily collaboration with Walt Disney. The Collection consists of 94 boxes of approximately 103 linear feet of materials. The majority of the collection consists of manuscript scores composed by Buddy Baker for Disney productions. The purposes of the scores fall under the broad categories of film, television, and theme parks, along with a fair amount of material whose production purpose is unspecified.
The collection includes various autograph, typed and photocopy versions of materials, including autograph scores, conductor short scores, sketches, typed scripts, vocal and orchestral parts, lead sheets, and music breakdown forms.
Arrangement
The Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection is arranged into four series in which the material is arranged alphabetically by production title.
Series I: Manuscript Scores by Buddy Baker
Series II: Manuscript Scores by Others
Series III: Assorted Media
Series IV: Miscellaneous.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
John Canemaker Animation Collection (MSS.040)
Separated Material
There is no information about materials that are associated by provenance to the described materials that have been physically separated or removed.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials that have not been preserved may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. Materials that have already been digitized are noted in the collection's finding aid and can be requested in our reading room. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Fales Library, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Correspondence.; Motion pictures (visual works); Sound recordings; Video recordings.; Amusement parks.; Scripts (documents); Scores.; Motion picture music -- United States.; Motion picture music -- Scores.; Television music; Motion picture music, Arranged.; Click tracks.; Film composers.; Animated film music.; Animated films.; Screenplays; Continuities.; Photocopies.; Sheets, Walter; Walt Disney Productions; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Bailey, Pearl; Sherman, Robert B.; Tatum, Shane; Brunner, Robert F.; Disney, Walt, 1901-1966; Tokyo Disneyland (Urayasu-shi, Japan); EPCOT Center (Fla.); University of Southern California
- Series I: Manuscript Scores by Buddy Baker
  - Adventure in the magic kingdom, An - Autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Autograph red and black pencil sketches; photocopy copyist's short score; annotated form
    General note
    5760
    1A-E, 2A-K, 3A-T, 4A-K, 5A-F, 6A-M1
    Walt and Dick - 1A; Tink - 1B; Tink-Toes - 1B1; Tinkerbell - 1C; You can fly - 1D; Mouse-dances - 2A; D-hotel - 2B; Plaque - 2C; Meet me down on mainstreet - 2D; Mainstreet - 2E-2H; Pan the lands - 2J; Jungle safari - 2K; More hippos - 3A; Head hunters - 3B; Dance, The - 3C; Gorilla - 3D; Falls, The - 3E; Tink's western dance - 3F; Gate's, The - 3G; Skirt - 3H; Villian (sic) - 3J; Dancing girls - 3K; Sluzy - 3L; Fifi - 3M; Pecos Bill and Can-Can - 3N; Mean-while! - 3O; Mexicana - 3P; Old mine piano - 3Q; Wagon train - 3R; Mining train - 3S; Rainbow cavern - 3T; Old west, The - 4A; Feather dance - 4B; Tom tom - 4C; Mark Twain boat and Indian song - 4D; Landing march - 4E; Jazz clar. - 4F; Clementine - 4F1; Sawyers island - 4G; Injun Joe - 4H; Ready - 4J; Attack - 4K; Future home - 5A; Auto pi a - 5B; Cotton picker Pete - 5C; Streamliner - 5D; Sky ride - 5E; Unbirthday song - 5F; Merrily song and Monstro - 6A; Story book land - 6B; Casey jr - 6C; English village - 6D; Castle - 6E; Flying - 6F; To the colors - 6G; To the colors #2 - 6H; Lights - 6J; Meet me down on main str. - 6K; Bar-B-Q blues - 6L; Shower of light - 6M; End title - 6M1
    Walt Disney Productions
  - African Pavillion World Showcase - Autograph and Photocopies - 37, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 74)
    Autograph red and black pencil full score, photocopy percussion part, Autograph black pencil percussion part
    03.J.1268.000
    Cue A-C
    Overture "When you wish upon a star" - Cue A; Overture "Item 18" - Cue B; Overture "Soldiers" - Cue C
    2 Fl, Ob, 2 Cl, Bsn, 3 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba, Perc, Timp, Gtr, Pf, Hp, 14 Vln, 8 Vla, 4 Cel, 3 Bs
  - America sings - Cues [Unnumbered and] 1-19, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    autograph black pencil, red ink short score and sketches
    J-0667-001
    1v-19(1)
    Yankee Doodle 1 South; Dixie - Cue 1v; Little Liza jane - 2v;Camptown - 3v;Bridge - 3v (1);Polly wolly - 5v (1);Heart rendering ditty - 5(2); Down in the valley - 7v - 7v(2);Pop goes the weasel - 7(3); Down by the riverside - 8v; Yankee doodle 2 - Western;Giddy up you all - 9; Drill - 9(1);Railroad - 10(1);Fireball - 11(1); Add guitar -12(1);Add marimba - 13(1);Pop goes the weasel - 13(2);Boot hill boys - 13(3);Yankee Doodle 3;Ball is over - 18(1);Bowery - 17(1);Wandering boy - 19(1)
    banjo,guitar,cb,tuba,drs,harmonica,vibes,piano,3cl,3trpt,ten,3trb,accordian,tuba,concertina
    Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; Walt Disney Productions
  - America sings - copies, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    photocopies of copyist's short scores
    J0667.001
    Unnumbered,Ev (opening),F,H, Iv,Kv,L,Unnumbered,1v-38
  - America sings - Cues A - L, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    autograph black pencil sketch, red and blue ink annotations
    Columbia, the gem of the ocean - Cue A; Yankee Doodle (opening) - Cue Ev; Yankee underscoe - Cue F;Happy - Cue G; Sad - Jeanne w/l br. Hair - Cue H & Jv; Pop goes the weasel - Cue Kv; Pop goes the weasel - Cue K(1);Travel on - Cue L
  - America sings - Sketches, 1973 Dec 26; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    autograph black pencil, black, blue, purple and red ink sketches and lead sheets
    Down by the riverside;Riverside;Yankee Doodle 2;Drill ye tarriers drill;Fireball mail;Old Chisholm trail;Who shot the hole in my sombrero;Billy the bad guy;Home on the range;Yankee Doodle 3;She may be somebody's mother;Where is my wandering boy tonight;Bill Bailey;And now,k blossom nose Murphy;Old grey mare;Bird in a gilded cage;Ta ra ra boom-de-ay; Yankee Doodle 4;Modern times;Beat me daddy;Hound dog;Shake rattle and roll;Twistin' U.S.A;Joy to the world;Yankee Doodle 5; Yankee Doodle 6; Auld lang syne
    Walt Disney Productions; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002
  - America Sings - Songs, etc. - Script, notes, etc., 1973 Nov 9, Dec 3-7; 1974 Jan 3-7, Feb. 13; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    Typed script; orchestra recording session schedules; photocopies of traditional music and music by other composers
  - America sings - Vocal parts, 1973 Dec 18; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    Autograph black pencil vocal parts with red pencil and black ink annotations;photocopy vocal parts
  - America sings autograph lead sheets, 1973 Dec 27, 1974 Jan 24; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    autograph black pencil, black, blue and red ink lead sheets; music breakdown forms filled in with autograph; autograph vocal breakdown sheet; typed song lists, revised script page
  - America sings Cues 20-38, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch with red ink annotations
    20(1)-38
    Bill Bailey - Cue 20(1);Pop goes the weasel - 20(2);Old grey mare - 22(1);Bird in a gilded cage - 23(1);Ta ra ra boom de ay - 24(1);Pop goes the Weasel - 24(2); Yankee Doodle 4 Jazz;Jada - Darktown - 25(1);Singing in the rain - 27(1);Tisket - 28(1);Boo hoo - 29(1);Beat me daddy 30(1);Pop goes the weasel - 30(3);Act alive - 30(4);Hound dog - 31(1);Alligator - 32(1);Shake rattle & roll - 33 (1); Twistin USA - 34(1);Joy to the world - 35(1);Yankee Doodle 5 modern;Yankee Doodle 6 - 36A and Auld lang syne B1;Good Bye goes the weasel - 37;Stars and stripes - 38
    stgs,tpts,tbns,tuba,piano,banjo,guit,bsn,2fl,2cl,drms,vibes
  - America Sings Lead sheets, 1973 Nov 8, 15, Dec 5, 18, 27; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 10 (Box 2)
    photocopy lead sheets with red and blue magic marker annotations
    J.0667.001
    Yankee Doodle opening;Jeanne with the light brown hair; Pop goes the weasel; Yankee Doodle 1; Dixie; Li'l Liza Jane;Campdown races; My old Kentucky home; Polly wolly Doodle; Single girl;Down in the valley;Down by the riverside; Yankee Doodle 2;Drill ye tarriers drill; I've been workin' on the railroad; Fire ball mail; Chisholm trail; Who shot the hole in my sombrero;Billy the bad guy; Home on the range; Yankee Doodle 3;She may be somebody's mother; Bowery, the;After the ball; Where is my wandering boy tonight?;Bill Bailey;Sweet Adeline; Old grey mare, the;Bird in a gilded cage;Ta ra ra boom de ay;Yankee Doodle 4;Jada; Dark Town Strutter's ball;Singin' in the rain; Tisket, a tasket, A;Boo hoo;Beat me Daddy; Joy to the world; Yankee Doodle 5; Yankee Doodle 6; Auld Lang Syne
  - America Sings script, etc., 1973 Ap 18, June 22, Oct 18;1974 Ap 29- May 3; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 2)
    Typed music breakdown form annotated with pencil, typed script, manuscript notes; color highlighted vocal breakdown sheet
    J0667-001
  - America the Beautiful - Autograph, 1967 Feb 27, Ap 13-14; Ward, Samuel (Box 44)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations;photocopy typescript;photocopy piano conductor short score; annotated music breakdown sheets, photocopy cue sheet,typed continuity
    5925-001;5925-006
    1JJJ-2SV
  - America the Beautiful - Cues 1JJJ-2CC; 1A-25V (Box 44)
  - America the Beautiful - full score with piano vocal scores (Box 44)
  - America the Beautiful - Music breakdown (Box 44)
  - America the Beautiful - script - 9, 27Feb-1 Mar, 13-14 Ap 1967; 6 (Box 44)
    typescript;music breakdown; typed continuity; autograph black pencil short score on 12 staff yellow paper with red and blue annotations; annotated photocopy copyist's piano conductor score; photocopy full score
    5925-001; 5925-006
    1JJJ, 1Jx, 1Jy1, JZ2CC;1A, 1Aalt, 1B, 1B3-18, 1Cv, 1Dv, 1Ev, 1Fv, 1G, 1G1, 1H, 1J, 1J1-2, 1Jy1-3, 1Jy1alt, 1JJ, 1JJ1, 1JJJ, 1JZ, 1K, 1K1, 1Lv, 1M, 1N, 1O, 1P, 1Q, 2A-C, 1CC, 2CC1, 2D, 2Ev, 2F-H, 2J-P, 2Q, 2Q1, 2Rv, 2Sv
    fl,pic,ob,Enghn,2cl,basscl,bsn,3tpt,3tbn,2hn,strings, harp, singers,pf,vib,percussion
    Bruns, George; Walt Disney Productions
  - American Adventure - Cues AAA1-AA33 (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - Miscellaneous (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - New World Bound - Autograph (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - Over There and New World Bound - Autographs (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - Piano Conductor photocopy (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - Storyboard (Box 45)
  - American Adventure - Timing sheet, music breakdown - 11, 14Oct, 4Nov 1981; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 9 (Box 45)
    annotated forms; autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red and green annotations; photocopy piano conductor score; autograph black pencil full score on 16 and 22 stave paper with red annotations
    03-J-1706;03-J-1706-004
    AA1-33
  - Apple Dumpling Gang - autograph - Cues X-2 [X-11], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 3)
    autograph pencil sketches with green, blue and red ink annotations
    0137
    X,1A-11Gv
    Buena Vista - Cue X;Donovan - 1A;Sweep in (1 & 2) -1CC;1B1 & 1B2;Apple dumpling gang - 1C4;Bushes - 1D2;Apple dumpling gang part 2 - 1Ev4;Kids - 2A;Gotta go - 2B;Hep Party - 2C;What to do? - 3A;Chickens - 3B;1st March - 3C;2nd March - 3D;3rd March - 3E;Snare Dr. only - 3F(1);Bass drum only - Cue 3F234567;Laundry - 3G;Saloon Pno 2 - 3H1-2;Mine, The - 3J;Mine car ride - 4A;Melodian 2 - 4B;Drs and hi hat - 4B1; I like you - 4C;4D1-2;Rooftop - 4E;Toms - 4E1;Oh me - 4F;Mister - 5A;Earthquake - 5B;Waterbowl - 5B1;Gold - 5C;Piece of cake - 5D;Torn dress - 6C;Marry dusty - 6D;Wittle Kids - 6E;Count of three - 7A;High ladder - 7B;Theo falls 7B1;Amos falls - 7B2;Rope - 7C;Trapped - 7D;Spy Glass - 8A;Wedding - 8B;Ceremony - 8C;Dusty's fury - 8D;Pno/Drs/Fender - 8D1;No place for a lady - 8E;Saloon pno 4 - 9A;Goodbye - 9B;Hold up - 9C;Firewagon - 10A; 10A1-2;Water scene -11A;Debris - 11B;Vault door - 11C;New dress - 11D;A-D-G, 11E2;A D G End title part 1 - 11Fv2;A D G End Title part II - 11 Gv
  - Apple Dumpling Gang - autograph sketches, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 3)
    autograph pencil lead sheets, sketch, timing notes
    ?v
    End title - vocal
  - Apple Dumpling Gang - Copyist's short scores, 1975 Feb 21, Ap 28-29 (Box 3)
    photocopies of copyist's short scores and lead sheats
    Unnumbered, 1A-11Gv, V
    Tatum, Shane; Walt Disney Productions
  - Apple Dumpling Gang - Music breakdown, etc., 1975 Mar 17-21, Ap 14-18, 21-25 (Box 3)
    music breakdown form with autograph pencil annotations, orchestra schedule form with typed additions, photocopy of music
  - Apple Dumpling Gang rides again - Autographs -Cues 1A-2D [1A-9], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 4)
    autograph black and red pencil sketch short score with red, blue and green ink annotations
    0179
    1A-9C
    Buena Vista - 1A;Synthesizer - 1A1; Theo and Ames 1 - 1B;Orch - 1B1;Synthesizer - 1B2;Fireloop - 1C;Flashpowder -1D;Willie Bill - 2A;Willie Bill guitars - 2A1;Synthesizer - 2A2;Bank - 2B;Escape - 2C;Willie Bill foiled - 2D;Synthesizer - 2D1;Rics - 2D1-8;Hurt - 3A;Synthesizer - 3A1;Swinger - 3B;Fall - 3B1;Slide - 3B2;Eye opener - 3C;In the wagon - 3D;Synthesizer - 3D1;Hi yo - 3E;Boy-girl theme - 3F;Enter fort - 4A;What's that? -4B;In the army - 4C;Feather - 4D;Party, The - 4E;Rock candy mt. - 4F/5A;Fire - 5B;Fire call - 5B1;5Balt;We heard him - 5C;Synthesizer - 5C1;Spin - 6A;He loves you - 6B;They're here - 6C;Jail birds - 7A;Big mac - 7A1;Jail birds TV -7AA;Ghost rides - 7B;Wait for me - 7C;Saloon Willy - 8A;Noon - 8B;Synthesizer - 8B1;Gay Pariesienne - 8C;Clementine - 8D;Break out - 8E;Boy-girl - 8F;Window - 9A;Rolling - 9A1;Theo and Amos - 9B; Theo and Amos (orch) - 9B1;Synthesizer - 9B2; Amos and Theo - 9C
  - Apple Dumpling gang rides again - Copies - Music Breakdown, etc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 3 (Box 4)
  - Apple Dumpling Gang rides again, copies - Piano Conductor, 1979 Mar 2, 5; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 4)
    photocopies copyist's synthesizer part and short scores
  - Aquamania - Autograph score - 29, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 45)
    photocopy piano conductor score; autograph black pencil score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    2499
    1A-E
  - Aquamania - Piano conductor - photocopy (Box 45)
  - Bayoo Boy - Sketches, texts, 1970 Sep 14-18, Oct 26-30; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 5)
    autograph pencil sketches, typed orch. recording schedule
    3593
    Marks; Walt Disney Productions
  - Bayou boy Cues 1-4 [1-12], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 5)
    autograph black and red pencil sketch short score
    1B-12G4
    Window - 1B;Harmot - 1C;Rowing - 2B;Cottage - 2D;Family - 2A;Verret - 2C;Supper - 2D1;Anguish - 2E;Lost bell - 2F;Jeannot leaves -2G;Crotalis -2G1;Bells - 2G2;More bells - 3A;Cone drops - 3B1;Hits Jeannot - 3B2;Pine cone - 3B;Crayfish - 3C;Dock - 4A;Like papa - 4B;Store - 4C;Can lid - 4C1;Lid 2 - 4C2;By Bayoo - 4D;Mailboat - 4E;Aboard - 4F;Clar - 4F1;Limb - 5A;Mr. Bob - 5B;Package - 5C;Fr. Boudreau - 5C1;Snorkel - 5D;Next day - 6A;Dark bayou - 6B;Rockofages - 6B1;Crow - 6C;Crow pt. 2 - 6C2;Crotalis - 6C1;Stand-off - 6D;Teeth 1; 6D1;Teeth 2 - 6D2;Gator - 6D3;Eyes 1 - 6D4;Eyes 2 - 6D5;Snap -6D6;6D7;Bayou boy reprise - 6Ev1;Charbot 2- 7A;Bayoo boy and hawk - 7B;Bars 61-63 - 7BB; Paint - 8A;Store 2 - 9A;Storm - 9B;Hawk - 9C;Lamp - 9D;Ringers - 9D1-3;Pirogue - 10Av1;A minor - 10Av3;Diffuse - 10B1;Wet treck - 10B;Snake 10C;Hit - 10C1;Find Jeannot - 10D;Lost sack - 10E;Lost? - 11A;Red eyes - 11B;Lasso - 11C;Snared -11D; Traps - 12A;Silver bell - 12A1;Distant bell - 12A2;Rescue - 12B;Injured - 12C;Chrbot & Bell - 12D;Conversation - 12E;Now is the time - 12F;Silver bell - 12G;Silver bell 2 - 12G1;Organ & Bayoo boy - 12G2;orch & Bayou boy;Bells & Bayou boy - 12G4
  - Bears and I, The - Autograph -Short score - Cues X-2 [X-10], 1974; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 6)
    autograph black pencil short score with red, green and blue ink annotations, yellow 12 stave paper
    3592
    X,A1V-10D
  - Bears and I, The - Copyist's short scores - Piano conductor, Music breakdown, 1974 Ao 3; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 6)
    photocopy copyist's short scores annotated with blue, green and red ink; typed order of takes, annotated music breakdown form
    X-1A1-10D
  - Bears and I, The - Sketches -Cues 1-2 [1-11], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 6)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch with red and green pencil and ink annotations, white 12 stave paper
    1D-11C
  - Beauvais Cathedral, undated (Box 7)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch, 12 stave yellow paper; autograph yellow, lined cue sheets
    1-6
  - Bluegrass Special, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 7)
    autograph black pencil 12 stave yellow short score sketch with blue, green and red ink annotations
    3765
    1A-6D
  - Boy who talked to Badgers, The, 1974 Nov 15, Dec 30-1975 Jan 3; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 7)
    photocopy cue sheets; typed, annotated notes on music; cue sheets annotated in red ink; annotated music breakdown sheet; orchestra recording schedule; autograph black pencil short score on yellow 12 stave paper with red and blue and green annotations
    3716
    1A-12C
    Sheets, Walter; Walt Disney Productions
  - Boy who flew the condors - Cues 1A-6F - Autograph (Box 46)
  - Boy who flew the condors - Music breakdown, 12-13 Dec 1966; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 46)
    autograph black pencil score on 18stave yellow paper with red annotations; annotated forms; copy piano conductor
    3385 TV
    1B-6F
  - Boy who flew the condors - Piano conductor - photocopy (Box 46)
  - Boy who stole the elephant, Sketches, Cues 1-4, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 7)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on white, 12 stave paper, with red pencil annotations
    3548
  - Canada '67 - Cues 1A-3K - Autograph (Box 47)
  - Canada '67 - Photocopy - Piano Conductor (Box 47)
  - Canada '67 - Script, music breakdown, 3, 22-26 Aug 1966; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 47)
    typscript;music breakdown;schedule of orchestra; autograph black pencil score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    5076-001
    1A-3K
    2fl,2ob, 4cl, bsn, 4 tpt, 3tbn,basstbn, 3perc, 3hn,baritone hn, 2tuba
  - Canada Circle Vision - Piano conductor 7, undated; 6 (Box 47)
    photocopy piano conductor
    J-1717;03-J-1715
    Pavillion Ent Music 1-3; Preshow 1-3;CP-C16
  - Carlo, the Sierra coyote, 1973 Dec 20-21; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 7)
    annotated music break down form, orchestra schedule; autograph black pencil, 12 stave yellow paper, short score with red, purple and blue annotations
    3623
    1A-6C
    Walt Disney Productions; Sheets, Walter
  - Castaway Cowboy, undated; Brunner, Robert F.; 8 (Box 7)
    photocopy copyist's short scores
    0115
    1A-10C1-X1(1)
  - Cat from Outer Space, 1978 Mar 16; Schifrin, Lalo; 5 (Box 8)
    photocopy copyist's short score; photocopy Kitty Kat Convention; photocopy cue sheet
    Logo (not used) CS 189- 1A-12D
  - Charley and Angel, 1973 Feb 1-2; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 8)
    autograph black pencil short score with red annotations on 12 stave white paper and 2 p. yellow paper; typed order of takes; music breakdown form annotated; schedule orchestra recording; manuscript blue ink Hello my baby; photocopies copyist "Hello my baby," "Three little words", pre-score You're driving me crazy, Cue 4B.
    0121 (TH)
    1A-10Gv,2E, X
  - China Pavilion Circle Vision - Autographs, 2-6 Aug 1982 (Box 74)
    music breakdown form; orchestra schedule; list of musicians; copy piano conductor or full score;manuscript and autograph black pencil full score on 12 and 32 staff yellow paper with red and blue annotations
    1A-2J1
  - China Pavilion Circle Vision - Photocopies with annotations (Box 74)
  - Christmas Album - Autograph - Short Score (Box 8)
  - Christmas Album - Autographs (Box 8)